Guide to the M. Perry Chapman papers, 1963-2010.
Chapman, M. Perry papers
- College and University Plans
  - Illinois - New York
    - New York
      - State University of New York at Buffalo Amherst Campus, 1970 (Box 9)
        Vol. 1: The Campus Plan
      - State University of New York at Buffalo Amherst Campus, 1970 (Box 9)
        Vol. 2: Design Vocabulary
      - Union College, 1984 (Box 12)
      - University at Albany, 2008 (Box 18)
        RPF for New Business School
      - University of Rochester River Corridor Study, 1986 (Box 3)
        Schematic Design Report
      - University of Rochester, 1972 (Box 10)
        Campus Development Plan/Landscape Master Plan
      - University of Rochester, 1975 (Box 10)
        Laser Fusion Laboratory/Site Design
      - University of Rochester, c. 1970-1973 (Box 10)
        Eastman School of Music: Sites
      - University of Rochester, c. 1968-1971 (Box 10)
        Misc. Site Evaluations and Reports
      - University of Rochester, 1972 (Box 10)
        Memo Report: Commercial Center for the U of Rochester
      - University of Rochester, 1977 (Box 10)
        Institutional Planned Development Application
      - University of Rochester, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
        River Campus Site Plan Study
      - University of Rochester, 1965 (Box 10)
        Campus Development Plan Progress Report NO. 1
      - University of Rochester, 1972 (Box 10)
        River Campus Sign Program
      - University of Rochester, 1966 (Box 10)
        Circulation Study Phase 1
      - University of Rochester, 1976 (Box 10)
        Circulation Study Phase 2
      - University of Rochester, 1985 (Box 10)
        Traffic and Parking Study
      - University of Rochester, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
        Eastman Dental Center: Site Evaluations
      - University of Rochester, 1967 (Box 10)
        Possible Family Housing Sites
      - Vassar, 1987 (Box 4)
        Interim Report: Inventory and Analysis
      - Vassar, 1987 (Box 4)
        Interim Report: Concept Alternatives
      - Vassar, 1988 (Box 4)
        Draft Report: The Landscape Master Plan
  - North Carolina - Wyoming; Canada and other Non- U.S. Campuses
    - North Carolina
      - Fayetteville State University, 1998 (Box 1)
        Draft Campus Master Plan Civil Engineering Technical Appendix
      - Fayetteville State University, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
        Master Plan Summary
      - North Carolina Central University, 1995 (Box 1)
        Inventory and Issues Report
      - North Carolina Central University, 1995 (Box 15)
      - North Carolina State University, 1989 (Box 1)
        Athletic Facilities Master Plan Executive Summary
      - North Carolina State University, Undated (Box 5)
        Athletic Facilities Master Plan
      - North Carolina State University, 1989 (Box 5)
        Centennial Center Site Location and Feasibility Study
      - University of North Carolina, Charlotte, Undated (Box 11)
      - University of North Carolina, Greensboro, 1992 (Box 1)
        Master Plan update
    - Ohio
      - Case Western Reserve University, Undated (Box 8)
        Master Campus Plan Final Report
      - Cleveland State University, 1971 (Box 3)
        Revised Master Plan
      - Cleveland State University, 1971 (Box 8)
      - Kent State University, 1965 (Box 8)
      - Ohio State University, 1998 (Box 7)
        Olentangy Plain District Plan
      - Ohio State University, 1997 (Box 7)
        South Campus District plan
      - Ohio State University, 1998 (Box 7)
        Parking Master Plan draft
      - Ohio State University, 1995 (Box 7)
        Campus Master Plan vol. 1 and 2
      - Ohio State University, 1998 (Box 7)
        Transportation and Parking Plan
      - Ohio State University, 1995 (Box 7)
        Campus Master Planning Process; Facilities Siting Study; Campus Master Plan Memoranda of Findings
      - Ohio State University, 1996 (Box 13)
        Academic Facilities Siting Study
      - Ohio State University, 1995 (Box 15)
      - University of Akron, Undated (Box 4)
        Campus Development Guide Plan Executive Summary
      - University of Cincinnati, 1998 (Box 6)
        Morgens, Scioto, and Sawyer Residence Halls Study
      - University of Cincinnati, 2000 (Box 9)
        Master Plan 2000
      - University of Cincinnati, Undated (Box 11)
        Campus Map
      - Wright State University, 1973 (Box 8)
        Concept Master Plan
    - Oklahoma
      - Oklahoma Christian College, 1971 (Box 8)
        Landscape and Development Guidelines
    - Oregon
      - Eastern Oregon University, 2001 (Box 2)
        Final Master Plan
      - Eastern Oregon University, 2002 (Box 2)
      - Lewis and Clark College, 1991 (Box 2)
        Campus Master Plan Summary of Findings from the Initial Work Session
      - Lewis and Clark College, 1991 (Box 2)
      - Lewis and Clark College, 1992 (Box 2)
        Estimate of Landscape Construction Costs
      - Lewis and Clark College, Undated (Box 2)
        Master Plans and Interventions Draft
    - Pennsylvania
      - Bloomsburg University, 1999 (Box 4)
        Campus Master Plan Round Two Alternatives Report
      - Bloomsburg University, 1999 (Box 4)
        Campus Master Plan Round One Alternatives Report
      - Carnegie Mellon University, 1967 (Box 8)
        Master Plan Studies Preliminary Report
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 7)
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1996-2016 (Box 13)
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 15)
        Master Plan draft
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 15)
        Master Plan Venango Campus draft
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 15)
        Schematic Cost Estimate
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, c. 1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        #51444.00 - Master Plan
      - Clarion University of Pennsylvania, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 10-20)
      - East Stroudsburg University, 1998 (Box 4)
        Campus Master Plan Phase III
      - East Stroudsburg University, 2000 (Box 8)
        Campus Facilities Master Plan
      - East Stroudsburg University, Undated (Box 8)
        Campus Master Plan - Draft
      - Lehigh University, 2000 (Box 4)
      - Lehigh University, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 37-38)
        (current) - Working papers
      - Lehigh University, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
        # 91481.96 - Working Papers
      - Milton Hershey School, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Penn State, 1989 (Box 12)
        University Park Campus Master Plan
      - University of Pennsylvania, 2006 (Box 15)
        Penn Connects: A Vision for the Future
      - University of Scranton, 1999 (Box 4)
        Campus Plan
    - Rhode Island
      - Brown University, 1998 (Box 4)
        Stretegic Facilities Planning Interview Supplement
      - Brown University, 1996 (Box 4)
        Preliminary Program and Site Selection Study
    - South Carolina
      - University of South Carolina, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Tennessee
      - East Tennessee State University, 1990 (Box 5)
        Preliminary Draft Campus Master Plan Phase 1: Inventory and Analysis Report
      - East Tennessee State University, 1990 (Box 13)
      - University of Tennessee, Knoxville, 1994 (Box 1)
      - Vanderbilt University, Undated (Box 5)
      - Vanderbilt University, 1973 (Box 6)
        The Second Hundred Years: a study of the development of Vanderbilt within the metropolitan Davidson County, TN
      - Vanderbilt University, 2001 (Box 15)
        Land Use and Development Plan
      - Vanderbilt University, Undated (Box 15)
        Alexander Hall Site Study
      - Vanderbilt University, 2001 (Box 15)
        Land Use and Development Plan Executive Summary
      - Vanderbilt University, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 27-33)
      - Vanderbilt University, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
        # 04488.96 - Working Papers
    - Texas
      - Rice University, 1998 (Box 18)
        Jones Graduate School of Management Architectural Program Statement
      - Southwestern University, 1992 (Box 2)
      - University of Texas Austin, Undated (Box 9)
    - Utah
      - Utah State University, 1998 (Box 2)
        Working papers and Campus Recreation Center Alternative Study
      - Utah State University, 2000 (Box 2)
        Precinct Plan Final Report
      - Utah State University, 2000 (Box 2)
        Master Plan Draft Report Campus Recreation
      - Utah State University, 2000 (Box 2)
      - Utah State University, 1999-2002 (Box 24, Folder 3-7)
      - Utah State University, 1996-1997 (Box 24)
        Fact Book
      - Utah State University, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Utah State University, 1996, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
        "History of Campus" and Master Plan
      - Utah State University, 1992 (Box 24)
        Vehicular and Pedestrian Traffic Study
      - Utah State University, 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        Campus Demographic Survey; Bicycle Parking Master Plan, Campus Map, photographs
    - Vermont
      - University of Vermont, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Virginia
      - Clinch Valley College, 1989 (Box 8)
      - George Mason University, 1987 (Box 1)
        Master Plan Executive Summary
      - James Madison University, 1988 (Box 13)
        Recreational Facilities Master Plan
      - Sweet Briar College, 1997 (Box 4)
        Interview Supplement Proposal for Comprehensive Master Plan
      - Sweet Briar College, 1998 (Box 15)
        Comprehensive Master Plan Presentation
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1971 (Box 5)
        Lambeth Field Site Accommodation Study
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Undated (Box 5)
        Development Plan
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1990 (Box 6)
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 2008 (Box 15)
        Grounds Plan
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1982 (Box 15)
        Comprehensive Development Plan
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1988 (Box 15)
        Traffic and Parking Analysis
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1985 (Box 15)
        An Evaluation of development potentials and strategies for the president of the University
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1990 (Box 15)
        President's Report
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1973 (Box 15)
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1988 (Box 15)
        Facilities Master Plan draft report summary
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1987 (Box 15)
        Draft Inventory Report
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1979 (Box 15)
        Birdwood Concept Plan Revision
      - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 1989 (Box 15)
        Facilities Master Plan; Accommodation Study for future university housing
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1993-2003 (Box 5)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1992 (Box 7)
        Six Year Capital Outlay Plan
    - West Virginia
      - West Virginia University, Undated (Box 1)
        Downtown Campus Master Plan
      - West Virginia University, 1986 (Box 1)
        Evansdale Campus Master Plan
      - West Virginia University, Undated (Box 5)
        Downtown Campus Master Plan Inventory Report
      - West Virginia University, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Wisconsin
      - Lawrence University, 2000 (Box 1)
        Update of Strategic Options
      - Marquette University, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Marquette University, 1992 (Box 7)
        Master Plan Technical Brief
      - Marquette University, 1992 (Box 7)
        Master Plan Draft Review: Goals, Programs, Phasing
      - Marquette University, 1992 (Box 7)
        Campus Master Plan draft with review with PPC
      - Marquette University, Undated (Box 7)
        Campus Master Plan Appendix
      - Marquette University, 1991 (Box 7)
        Master Plan Supplement
      - Marquette University, 1992 (Box 7)
      - University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1993 (Box 12)
        Parking Demand/Impact Study
    - Wyoming
      - Western Wyoming College, 1982 (Box 2)
        Preliminary Program Analysis
      - Western Wyoming College, Undated (Box 2)
      - Western Wyoming College, 1982 (Box 2)
        Draft Master Plan Report
    - Canada and Non-U.S. Campuses
      - American University in Beirut, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        Vision and Mission Information; Master Plan
      - University of Windsor, 1988 (Box 12)
      - "Integration and Interaction: Redesign the Campus of Wuhan University, China", 2007 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Business School Related
    - University of Wyoming, 2005 (Box 17)
      Level 1 Planning Report - Binder
    - University of Wyoming, 2005 (Box 17)
      Level 1 Planning Report
    - University of Wyoming, 2006 (Box 17)
      Level II Planning Study
    - University of Wyoming, 2006 (Box 17)
      Level II Planning Study: Schematic Design Workshop 1, 2, 3 & 4
    - University of Wyoming, 2006 (Box 17)
      Interview for Level II Services
    - University of Wyoming, 2005 (Box 17)
      Peer Institution Analysis
    - University of New Hampshire, Undated (Box 17)
      New Business School Interview Presentation
    - University of New Hampshire, 2008 (Box 17)
      RPF for Whittemore Business School
    - University of Texas Austin, 2009 (Box 17)
      Strategic Master Plan for the McCombs School of Business
    - University of California San Diego, 2001 (Box 18)
      Detailed Project Program Appendix
    - University of California San Diego, 2001 (Box 18)
      Detailed Project Program
    - University of California San Diego, 2001 (Box 18)
      Management School Project: Fees and Contract Issues
    - Supporting Business School Education, Undated (Box 18)
      Sasaki Brochure
    - University of Western Ontario, 2008 (Box 18)
      Richard Ivey School of Business
    - Georgia State University, 2009 (Box 18)
      Detailed Facility Programming and Concept Development
    - Rice University, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Ohio State University, 1993 (Box 18)
      College of Business Phase I Planning
    - University of California Berkeley, 2005 (Box 18)
      Executive Education Facility State of Interest
    - University of Pennsylvania, 2008 (Box 18)
      Wharton School Programming, Site Analysis, and Feasibility Services
    - University at Albany, 2008 (Box 18)
    - Morgan State University, 2010 (Box 18)
      Business School Oral Presentation
    - Morgan State University, 2010; CD-2222 (Box 18)
    - Radford University, 2008 (Box 18)
    - Stanford University, 1995 (Box 18)
      Graduate School of Business Residential Learning Center
    - Stanford University, 1995 (Box 18)
      Graduate School of Business Residential Learning Center: Program Report
    - Stanford University, 1995 (Box 18)
    - Washington University, 2001 (Box 18)
      Simon Hall Programming Study - Final Report
    - Washington University, 1997 (Box 18)
      John M. Olin School of Business: Memos and Reports
    - Washington University, 1998 (Box 18)
      John M. Olin School of Business: Pre: Design Report
    - Washington University, 1996 (Box 18)
      John M. Olin School of Business: Project 21 Report
    - University of Virginia, 1992 (Box 18)
      Darden School Design Competition
    - Emory University, 2006 (Box 18)
      The Balser Art Collection at Emory University's Goizueta Business School
    - University of Utah, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      David Eccles School of Business: Master Plan Update
    - Northern Arizona University, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - West Chester University, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Undergraduate Business Center Project Design
    - Saint Leo University, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Letter of Interest for Business School
    - Business School Design Strategies, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - University of California San Diego, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      DPP Fee
    - University of California San Diego, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Distribution Fees
    - University of California San Diego, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Fees
    - Business School Status Summaries, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      File contains study for the Olin School of Business
    - Ohio State University, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Replacement Facilities for the College of Business
    - Sasaki Business School Work, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Reports
    - Business School Articles, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Business Schools Green, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Articles on sustainable ideas in the business school curriculum
    - University of Illinois, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      College of Business - Memos and Analysis
    - Ohio State University, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      College of Business - New Facilities revisions
    - Washington University, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      Knight Center for Executive Education
    - Business School Costs, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Business School Statistics, 1995-2009 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - University of California San Diego, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      Project Budget
    - International Business Schools, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Royal Bank of Scotland, Undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Olympic Games
  - 1980 Winter Olympics, 1976 (Box 3)
    Material Submitted for April 5 Task Force Meeting
  - 1980 Winter Olympics, 1976 (Box 3)
    Application for Project Permit for 90 & 70 Meter Ski Jump Facility
  - 1980 Winter Olympics, 1977 (Box 3)
    Application for Project Permit for the Field House Complex
  - 1980 Winter Olympics, 1978 (Box 3)
    Draft Supplementary Environmental Impact Statement
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1979 (Box 8)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Temporary Housing
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1977 (Box 14)
    Final Environmental Impact Statement
  - 1980 Olympic Games, Undated (Box 14)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Draft Transportation Plan
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1978 (Box 14)
    Final Supplementary Environmental Impact Statement
  - 1980 Olympic Games, Undated (Box 14)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Parking Lots
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1979 (Box 14)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Temporary Support Personnel Housing
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1978 (Box 14)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Horse Show Grounds Proposed Actions
  - 1980 Olympic Games, Undated (Box 14)
    Supplementary Environmental Assessments: Mt. Van Hoevenberg Uphill Transportation
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1976 (Box 14)
    Working Brief #2: Study Organization and Schedule for Agency Interaction
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1979 (Box 14)
    Environmental Report Concerning Uphill Transportation Alternatives for the Mt. Van Hoevenberg Bobsled and Luge Complex
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1979 (Box 14)
    Mitigation Plan for Temporary Support Personnel Housing at Cold Brook Plaza
  - 1980 Olympic Games, Undated (Box 14)
    Workbook Draft for Task Force Review Environmental Assessment Report
  - 1980 Olympic Games, 1975 (Box 14)
    Proposal for Environmental Impact Assessment
  - 1984 Olympic Games Los Angeles, 1981 (Box 14)
  - 1984 Olympic Games Los Angeles, 1980 (Box 17)
    Environmental Impact Report/Statement
- City Planning
  - Capital City for Alaska, Undated (Box 2)
    Summary Proposed Capital City for Alaska
  - Arsenal Park Urban Renewal Project, 1969 (Box 3)
    Master Development Plan
  - Arsenal Park Urban Renewal Project, Undated (Box 3)
    Design Review
  - Arsenal Park Urban Renewal Project, 1979 (Box 3)
    Physical Planning and Design Evaluation of Developer Proposal
  - Genesee River South Corridor, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Guilford/B&M Properties, 1987 (Box 3)
    Preliminary Feasibility Study
  - Lawrence Mills Site Redevelopment, Undated (Box 3)
    Executive Summary
  - Mayo Clinic, 1967 (Box 3)
    Medical Center Master Plan
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Rochester- Monroe Country Metropolitan Area, 1964 (Box 3)
    Design for the future: A master plan
  - Rochester, New York, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Rochester, New York, 1963 (Box 3)
    Community Renewal Program
  - Rochester, New York, 1965 (Box 3)
    The Future of Downtown Rochester
  - Rochester Science Park, 1985 (Box 3)
    Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement Appendices
  - Rochester Science Park, 1985 (Box 3)
    Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement
  - Watertown Redevelopment Authority, 1979 (Box 3)
    Evaluation of Developer Proposals
  - Worcester Biomedical Research Park, 1984 (Box 3)
    Draft Environmental Impact Report
  - Brickyard Mountain, Undated (Box 6)
    A Preliminary evaluation of the development potential for Brickyard Mtn. at Lake Winnipesaukee, Laconia NH
  - The Genesee River Study, 1965 (Box 6)
    A technical and visual analysis
  - Watertown Lectures, Undated (Box 7)
    Study Manual, Source Notes, and Bibliography
  - Woolwich Township, 1975 (Box 7)
    Density Evaluation for Planned Unit Developments
  - Woolwich Township, 1975 (Box 7)
    Proposed Zoning Regulations and Amendments
  - Woolwich Township, 1975 (Box 7)
    Proposed Zoning Regulations and Amendments - Revised Planner's Draft
  - Woolwich Township, 1975 (Box 7)
    Proposed Zoning Regulations and Amendments - Final Draft
  - Woolwich Township, 1975 (Box 7)
    Zoning Update
  - Woolwich Township, 1976 (Box 7)
    Proposed New Site Plan Review Ordinance and Subdivision Ordinance: Revised Planner's Draft
  - Woolwich Township, 1988 (Box 7)
    Long Range Land Use Plan
  - Woolwich Township, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Hamot Health Systems, Inc., 1987 (Box 8)
  - University Circle, 1990 (Box 8)
    A Guide for the Future: master Plan
  - East Hill Plaza, Undated (Box 9)
    Sub-Area Accommodation Study
  - Rochester, New York, 1984 (Box 10)
    Genesee River South Corridor Land Use and Development Plan
  - Rochester, New York, 1974 (Box 10)
    Institutional District Zoning
  - Columbia, Missouri, 2007 (Box 11)
    Storm water Management and Water Quality Manual
  - Altid Enterprises Property, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Granite Pond Stonehenge, 1989 (Box 13)
    Chronology: 1986-1989
  - Charleston Waterfront Park, 1980 (Box 14)
  - New York State Canal Recreationway Plan, 1995 (Box 14)
    Draft
  - Sepulveda Basin, 1980 (Box 14)
    Planning Workbook updated Master Plan and Environmental Impact Report
  - Sepulveda Basin, 1981 (Box 14)
    Master Plan and Final Environmental Impact Statement
  - Boston Harbor, Undated (Box 17)
    Challenges and Opportunities for the 1980's
  - Casey-Almond Road Area, 1980 (Box 17)
    Planning Study
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1981 (Box 17)
    Land Resource Evaluation
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1984 (Box 17)
    Boundary Requirements and Development Criteria Carrs Hill Site
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1986 (Box 17)
    Growth Area
  - Columbia, South Carolina, 2007 (Box 17)
    Innovista Master Plan
  - Commerce Park at Middleborough Circle, 1983 (Box 17)
    Design and Development Standards
  - Donnelley/Ketting Land Planning Study, 1982 (Box 17)
    Analysis for Agricultural Land/Open Space retention and limited development
  - Engelhard Realty Tract #2 in Monroe Township, NJ, 1974 (Box 17)
    Reconnaissance Survey and Evaluation
  - Greystone Pond, Undated (Box 17)
    Master plan environmental assessment
  - Lighthouse Point, 1971 (Box 17)
    Feasibility Study/ Concept Plan
  - Long Wharf, Undated (Box 17)
    poster
  - Massachusetts Microelectronics Center, 1983 (Box 17)
    RFP
  - Middlesex County Training School Site, Undated (Box 17)
  - Minnewaska State Park, 1981 (Box 17)
    Master Plan Appendix
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1981 (Box 17)
    Visual Impact Assessment
  - Pennichuck Water Works, 1979 (Box 17)
    Feasibility Study
  - Pennichuck Water Works, 1980 (Box 17)
    Evaluation of water works landholdings as they relate to water quality and supply
  - Pennichuck Water Works, 1984 (Box 17)
    Turnpike Area master plan